export const questions = [
  {
    question: "When did the US gain its independence?",
    answer: "July 4, 1776",
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the first elected president of the US?",
    answer: "George Washington",
  },
  {
    question: "Who approved the Declaration of Independence?",
    answer: "The Continental Congress",
  },
  {
    question: "How many states were formed after the US declared independence?",
    answer: "13",
  },
  {
    question: "Was Texas part of the original 13 colonies?",
    answer:
      "False. The 13 were New Hampshire, Massachusetts, Rhode Island, Connecticut, New York, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, Delaware, Maryland, Virginia, North Carolina, South Carolina, and Georgia.",
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the 16th president?",
    answer: "Abraham Lincoln",
  },
  {
    question: "What was the 1st American war?",
    answer: "The Revolutionary War",
  },
  {
    question: "What city was the first capital of the United States?",
    answer: "New York City",
  },
  {
    question: "When was the first U.S. dollar printed?",
    answer: "1862",
  },
  {
    question: "What year did the United States enter World War 1?",
    answer: "1917",
  },
];
